<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<pim revno="0" chngno="0" dmwr-inclus="parts">
	<titlepg maintlvl="maintainer">
        <name>WIRE NEUTRALIZATION SYSTEM</name>
    </titlepg>

	<!-- ********** RPSTL INTRO ********** -->
	
	<introwp wpno="r002092355461" chngno="0">
        <wpidinfo>
            <maintlvl level="maintainer"/>
            <title>REPAIR PARTS AND SPECIAL TOOLS LIST (RPSTL) INTRODUCTION.<indxref
                    ref1="Repair Parts and Special Tool List (RPSTL) introduction."/></title>
        </wpidinfo>
        <title>SCOPE</title>
        <para>This RPSTL lists the authorized spares and repair parts; special tools, special test,
            measurement, and diagnostic equipment (TMDE); and other special support equipment
            required for performance of maintainer level maintenance of the Explosively Formed
            Penetrator Armor Kit. It authorizes the requisitioning, issue, and disposition of
            spares, repair parts, and special tools as indicated by the source, maintenance, and
            recoverability (SMR) codes.</para>
        <title>GENERAL</title>
        <para>In addition to the Introduction work package, this RPSTL is divided into the following
            work packages. <seqlist>
                <item>Repair Parts List Work Packages. Work packages containing lists of spare and
                    repair parts authorized by this RPSTL for use in the performance of maintenance.
                    These work packages also include parts which must be removed for replacement of
                    the authorized parts. Parts lists are composed of functional groups in ascending
                    alphanumeric sequence, with the parts in each group listed in ascending figure
                    and item number sequence. Sending units, brackets, filters and bolts are listed
                    with the component they mount on. Repair parts kits are listed separately in
                    their own functional group and work package. Items listed are shown on the
                    associated illustrations. </item>

                <item>Cross-Reference Indexes Work Packages. There are two cross-reference index
                    work packages in this RPSTL: the National Stock Number (NSN) Index work package
                    and the Part Number (P/N) Index work package. The National Stock Number Index
                    work package refers you to the figure and item number. The Part Number Index
                    work package refers you to the figure and item number for each part number
                    listed in the RPSTL. </item>
            </seqlist>
        </para>
        <title>EXPLANATION OF COLUMNS IN THE REPAIR PARTS LIST AND SPECIAL TOOLS LIST WORK
            PACKAGES</title>
        <para>ITEM NO. (Column (1)). Indicates the number used to identify items called out in the
            illustration.</para>
        <para>SMR CODE (Column (2)). The SMR code containing supply/requisitioning information,
            maintenance level authorization criteria and disposition instruction, as shown in the
            following breakout. This entry may be subdivided into 4 subentries, one for each
            service. <table frame="none" id="r002092355461-Table-1">
                <title>SMR Code Explanation</title>
                <tgroup cols="3" align="center" colsep="1">
                    <tbody>
                        <row>
                            <entry><emphasis emph="bold"/>Source<?Pub _newline?>
                                Code<?Pub _newline?> XX</entry>
                            <entry><emphasis emph="bold"/>Maintenance<?Pub _newline?>
                                Code<?Pub _newline?> XX:</entry>
                            <entry><emphasis emph="bold"/>Recoverability Code<?Pub _newline?>
                                Code<?Pub _newline?> X</entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry align="left">1st two positions: <?Pub _newline?>How to get an
                                item.</entry>
                            <entry align="left">3rd position: <?Pub _newline?> 4th position: Who can
                                install, replace or use the item. Who can do complete repair on the
                                item. <?Pub _newline?>
                            </entry>
                            <entry align="left">5th position:<?Pub _newline?> Who determines
                                disposition action on unserviceable items.</entry>
                        </row>
                    </tbody>
                </tgroup>
            </table>
        </para>
        <?Pub _newpage?>
        <note>
            <trim.para>Complete Repair: Maintenance capacity, capability, and authority to perform
                all corrective maintenance tasks of the "Repair" function in a use/user environment
                in order to restore serviceability to a failed item.</trim.para>
        </note>
        <para>Source Code. The source code tells you how you get an item needed for maintenance,
            repair, or overhaul of an end item/equipment. Explanations of source codes follow:
                <table colsep="1" frame="all" rowsep="1" id="r002092355461-Table-2">
                <title>Source Code Explanation</title>
                <tgroup cols="2">
                    <colspec align="center" colname="c1" colnum="1" colwidth="1.25in" rowsep="1"/>
                    <colspec colname="c2" colnum="2" colsep="1" colwidth="5.75in" rowsep="1"/>
                    <thead>
                        <row>
                            <entry align="center">
                                <emphasis emph="uline">Source Code</emphasis>
                            </entry>
                            <entry align="center">
                                <emphasis emph="uline">Application/Explanation</emphasis>
                            </entry>
                        </row>
                    </thead>
                    <tbody>
                        <row rowsep="1">
                            <entry rowsep="1">PA </entry>
                            <entry colsep="1" morerows="9" rowsep="1" valign="middle">Stock items;
                                use the applicable NSN to requisition/request items with these
                                source codes. They are authorized to the level indicated by the code
                                entered in the third position of the SMR code. <note>
                                    <trim.para>Items coded PC are subject to deterioration. Items
                                        coded PR or PZ <?Pub _newline?>are obsolete and may not be
                                        able to be ordered like other P coded items. </trim.para>
                                </note>
                            </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">PB </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>PC </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">PD </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">PE </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="1">
                            <entry rowsep="1">PF </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="1">
                            <entry rowsep="1">PG </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">PH </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">PR </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="1">
                            <?PubTbl row rht="0.38in"?>
                            <entry rowsep="1">PZ </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>KD </entry>
                            <entry morerows="2" valign="middle">Items with these codes are not to be
                                requested/requisitioned individually. They are part of a kit which
                                is authorized to the maintenance level indicated in the third
                                position of the SMR code. The complete kit must be requisitioned and
                                applied. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>KF </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>KB </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>MF-Made at maintainer class </entry>
                            <entry morerows="4" valign="middle">Items with these codes are not to be
                                requisitioned/requested individually. They must be made from bulk
                                material which is identified by the P/N in the DESCRIPTION AND
                                USABLE ON CODE (UOC) entry and listed in the bulk material group
                                work package of the PI. If the item is authorized to you by the
                                third position code of the SMR code, but the source code indicates
                                it is made at higher level, order the item from the higher level of
                                maintenance. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <!--<entry>MF-Made at
                                maintainer class
                            </entry>-->
                            <entry>MH-Made at below depot sustainment class </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>ML-Made at SRA </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>MD-Made at depot </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="1">
                            <entry>MG-Navy only </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>AF-Assembled by maintainer class </entry>
                            <entry morerows="4" valign="middle">Items with these codes are not to be
                                requested/requisitioned individually. The parts that make up the
                                assembled item must be requisitioned or fabricated and assembled at
                                the level of maintenance indicated by the source code. If the third
                                position of the SMR code authorizes you to replace the item, but the
                                source code indicates the item is assembled at a higher level, order
                                the item from the higher level of maintenance. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>AH-Assembled by below depot sustainment class </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>AL-Assembled by SRA </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry>AD-Assembled by depot </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="1">
                            <entry>AG-Navy only </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">XA </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1" valign="middle">Do not requisition an
                                "XA" coded item. Order the next higher assembly. (Refer to NOTE
                                below). </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">XB </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">If an item is not available from salvage,
                                order it using the CAGEC and P/N. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">XC</entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Installation drawings, diagrams,
                                instruction sheets, field service drawings; identified by
                                manufacturer P/N. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">XD </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Item is not stocked. Order an "XD" coded
                                item through local purchase or normal supply channels using the
                                CAGEC and P/N given, if no NSN is available. </entry>
                        </row>
                    </tbody>
                </tgroup>
            </table>
        </para>
        <note>
            <trim.para>Cannibalization or controlled exchange, when authorized, may be used as a
                source of supply for items with the above source codes except for those items source
                coded "XA" or those aircraft support items restricted by requirements of AR
                750-1.</trim.para>
        </note>
        <para>Maintenance Code. Maintenance codes tell you the level(s) of maintenance authorized to
            use and repair support items. The maintenance codes are entered in the third and fourth
            positions of the SMR code as follows:</para>
        <para>Third Position. The maintenance code entered in the third position tells you the
            lowest maintenance class authorized to remove, replace, and use an item. The maintenance
            code entered in the third position will indicate authorization to the following classes
            of maintenance: <table>
                <tgroup colsep="1" rowsep="1" cols="2" tgroupstyle="nolabel">
                    <colspec align="center" colname="c1" colnum="1" colwidth="1.25in" rowsep="1"/>
                    <colspec colname="c2" colnum="2" colsep="1" colwidth="5.75in" rowsep="1"/>
                    <thead>
                        <row>
                            <entry align="center">
                                <emphasis emph="uline"><emphasis emph="bold">Maintenance
                                        Code</emphasis></emphasis>
                            </entry>
                            <entry align="center">
                                <emphasis emph="uline"><emphasis emph="bold"
                                        >Application/Explanation</emphasis></emphasis>
                            </entry>
                        </row>
                    </thead>
                    <tbody>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">C - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Crew </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">F - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Maintainer maintenance can remove,
                                replace, and use the item. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">H - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Below Depot Sustainment maintenance can
                                remove, replace, and use the item.</entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="1">
                            <entry rowsep="1">L - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Specialized repair activity can remove,
                                replace, and use the item.</entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="1">
                            <entry rowsep="1">G - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Afloat and ashore intermediate
                                maintenance can remove, replace, and use the item (Navy
                                only).</entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">K - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Contractor facility can remove, replace,
                                and use the item.</entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">Z - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Item is not authorized to be removed,
                                replace, or used at any maintenance level.</entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1">D - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Depot can remove, replace, and use the
                                item.</entry>
                        </row>
                    </tbody>
                </tgroup>
            </table>
        </para>
        <note>
            <trim.para>Army will use C in the third position. However, for joint service
                publications, other services may use O.</trim.para>
        </note>
        <para>Fourth Position. The maintenance code entered in the fourth position tells you whether
            or not the item is to be repaired and identifies the lowest maintenance class with the
            capability to do complete repair (perform all authorized repair functions). <table>
                <tgroup cols="2" tgroupstyle="nolabel">
                    <tbody>
                        <row>
                            <entry align="center">
                                <emphasis emph="uline"><emphasis emph="bold">Maintenance
                                        Code</emphasis></emphasis>
                            </entry>
                            <entry align="center">
                                <emphasis emph="uline"><emphasis emph="bold"
                                        >Application/Explanation</emphasis></emphasis>
                            </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">C - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Crew (operator) is the lowest class that
                                can do complete repair.</entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">F - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Maintainer is the lowest class that can
                                do complete repair of the item. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">H - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Below Depot Sustainment is the lowest
                                class that can do complete repair of the item. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">L - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Specialized repair activity (enter
                                specialized repair activity designator) is the lowest class that can
                                do complete repair of the item. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">D - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Depot is the lowest class that can do
                                complete repair of the item. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">G - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Both afloat and ashore intermediate
                                levels are capable of complete repair of item. (Navy only). </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">K - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Complete repair is done at contractor
                                facility. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">Z - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Nonreparable. No repair is authorized.
                            </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">B - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">No repair is authorized. No parts or
                                special tools are authorized for maintenance of "B" coded item.
                                However, the item may be reconditioned by adjusting, lubricating,
                                etc., at the user level. </entry>
                        </row>
                    </tbody>
                </tgroup>
            </table>
        </para>
        <para>Recoverability Code. Recoverability codes are assigned to items to indicate the
            disposition action on unserviceable items. The recoverability code is shown in the fifth
            position of the SMR code as follows:<table>
                <tgroup cols="2" tgroupstyle="nolabel">
                    <tbody>
                        <row>
                            <entry align="center">
                                <emphasis emph="uline"><emphasis emph="bold">Recoverability
                                        Code</emphasis></emphasis>
                            </entry>
                            <entry align="center">
                                <emphasis emph="uline"><emphasis emph="bold"
                                        >Application/Explanation</emphasis></emphasis>
                            </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">C - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Reparable item. When uneconomically
                                reparable, condemn and dispose of the item at the crew/operator
                                level.</entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">Z - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Nonreparable item. When unserviceable,
                                condemn and dispose of the item at the level of maintenance shown in
                                the third position of the SMR code. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">F - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Reparable item. When uneconomically
                                reparable, condemn and dispose of the item at the field level.
                            </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">H - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Reparable item. When uneconomically
                                reparable, condemn and dispose of the item at the below depot
                                sustainment. </entry>
                        </row>

                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">D - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Reparable item. When beyond lower level
                                repair capability, return to depot. Condemnation and disposal of
                                item are not authorized below depot. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">L - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Reparable item. Condemnation and disposal
                                not authorized below Specialized Repair Activity (SRA). </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">A - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Item requires special handling or
                                condemnation procedures because of specific reasons (such as
                                precious metal content, high dollar value, critical material, or
                                hazardous material). Refer to appropriate manuals/directives for
                                specific instructions. </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">G - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Field level reparable item. Condemn and
                                dispose at either afloat or ashore intermediate levels. (Navy only).
                            </entry>
                        </row>
                        <row rowsep="0">
                            <entry rowsep="1" align="center">K - </entry>
                            <entry align="left" rowsep="1">Reparable item. Condemnation and disposal
                                to be performed at contractor facility. </entry>
                        </row>
                    </tbody>
                </tgroup>
            </table>
        </para>
        <para>NSN (Column (3)). The NSN(s) for the item is listed in this column. </para>
        <para>CAGEC (Column (4)). The Commercial and Government Entity Code (CAGEC) is a five-digit
            code which is used to identify the manufacturer, distributor, or Government
            agency/activity that supplies the item. </para>
        <para>PART NUMBER (Column (5)). Indicates the primary number used by the manufacturer
            (individual, company, firm, corporation, or Government activity), which controls the
            design and characteristics of the item by means of its engineering drawings,
            specifications, standards, and inspection requirements to identify an item or range of
            items.</para>
        <note>
            <trim.para>When you use an NSN to requisition an item, the item you receive may have a
                different part number from the number listed. </trim.para>
        </note>
        <para>DESCRIPTION AND USABLE ON CODE (UOC) (Column (6)). This column includes the following
            information: <seqlist>
                <item>The federal item name, and when required, a minimum description to identify
                    the item. </item>
                <item>Part numbers of any bulk materials required if the item is to be locally
                    manufactured or fabricated. </item>
                <item>Hardness Critical Item (HCI). Items that require special handling or
                    procedures to ensure protection against electromagnetic pulse (EMP) damage are
                    marked with the letters ‘HCI'. </item>
                <item>Refer to Usable on Code details presented later in this work package under
                    SPECIAL INFORMATION. </item>
                <item>Dot indentions indicate the relationship of the part (or parts) to its next
                    higher assembly (NHA) in the tabular listing. The NHA for this part (or parts)
                    is listed right before the part (or parts) that it is the NHA for. If the item
                    is connected directly to (can be disassembled from) the item identified in the
                    functional group code title for that specific tabular listing, it shall have one
                    dot indentation. Otherwise, that item in the tabular list will not have a dot
                    indention. </item>
                <item>The statement END OF FIGURE appears below the last item description in column
                    (6) for each Figure in the repair parts list, special tools repair parts, kits,
                    bulk items, and special tools list work packages. </item>
            </seqlist>
        </para>
        <para>QTY (Column (7)). The QTY (quantity per Figure) column indicates the quantity of the
            item used in the breakout shown on the illustration/Figure. A "V" appearing in this
            column instead of a quantity indicates that the quantity is variable and quantity may
            change from application to application. </para>
        <!--<para>(MC) Include in multiservice manuals involving Marine Corps. USMC QTY per Equip
            (Column (8)). </para>-->
        <para>This column indicates the total quantity of the item used on the equipment. </para>
        <title>EXPLANATION OF CROSS-REFERENCE INDEXES WORK PACKAGES FORMAT AND COLUMNS</title>
        <para>
            <seqlist>
                <item>National Stock Number (NSN) Index Work Package. NSNs in this index are listed
                    in National Item Identification Number (NIIN) sequence. <randlist>
                        <item>STOCK NUMBER Column. This column lists the NSN in NIIN sequence. The
                            NIIN consists of the last nine digits of the NSN. When using this column
                            to locate an item, ignore the first four digits of the NSN. However, the
                            complete NSN should be used when ordering items by stock number. </item>
                        <item>For example, if the NSN is 5385-01-574-1476, the NIIN is
                            01-574-1476.</item>
                        <item>FIG. Column. This column lists the number of the Figure where the item
                            is identified/located. The Figures are in numerical order in the repair
                            parts list and special tools list work packages.</item>
                        <item>ITEM Column. This column identifies the item associated with the
                            Figure listed in the adjacent FIG. column. This item is also identified
                            by the NSN listed on the same line.</item>
                    </randlist>
                </item>
                <item>Part Number (P/N) Index Work Package. Part numbers which are all numbers are
                    listed first in ascending numeric sequence. Part numbers containing letters and
                    numbers are listed in ascending alphanumeric sequence by part number after all
                    the part numbers containing numbers only.<randlist>
                        <item>PART NUMBER Column. This column indicates the part number assigned to
                            the item.</item>
                        <item>FIG. Column. This column lists the number of the Figure where the item
                            is identified/located in the repair parts list and special tools list
                            work packages.</item>
                        <item>ITEM Column. The item number is the number assigned to the item as it
                            appears in the Figure referenced in the adjacent Figure number
                            column.</item>
                    </randlist></item>

            </seqlist>
        </para>

        <title>SPECIAL INFORMATION</title>

        <para>UOC. The UOC appears in the lower left corner of the Description Column heading.
            Usable on codes are shown as "UOC:" in the Description Column (justified left) on the
            first line under the applicable item/nomenclature. Uncoded items are applicable to all
            models. Examples of the UOCs used in the RPSTL are: <table>
                <tgroup cols="2" tgroupstyle="nolabel">
                    <tbody>
                        <row>
                            <entry align="center"><emphasis emph="uline"/><emphasis emph="bold"
                                    >Code</emphasis></entry>
                            <entry align="center"><emphasis emph="uline"/><emphasis emph="bold">Used
                                    On</emphasis></entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry align="center">RG-3</entry>
                            <entry align="center">MMPV TYPE II M1270</entry>
                        </row>
                    </tbody>
                </tgroup>
            </table>
        </para>
        <para>Associated Publications. The publication(s) listed below pertain to the (Explosively
            Formed Penetrator (EFP) armor kit): <table>
                <tgroup cols="2" tgroupstyle="nolabel">
                    <tbody>
                        <row>
                            <entry align="center"><emphasis emph="uline"><emphasis emph="bold"
                                        >Publication</emphasis></emphasis></entry>
                            <entry align="center"><emphasis emph="uline"><emphasis emph="bold">Short
                                        Title</emphasis></emphasis></entry>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <entry align="center">None</entry>
                        </row>

                    </tbody>
                </tgroup>
            </table>
        </para>
        <title>HOW TO LOCATE REPAIR PARTS</title>
        <para>
            <seqlist>
                <item>When NSNs or Part Numbers Are Not Known.</item>
            </seqlist>
            <randlist>
                <item>First. Using the table of contents, determine the assembly group to which the
                    item belongs. This is necessary since Figures are prepared for assembly groups
                    and subassembly groups, and lists are divided into the same groups. </item>
                <item>Second. Find the Figure covering the functional group or the sub functional
                    group to which the item belongs. </item>
                <item>Third. Identify the item on the Figure and note the number(s).</item>
                <item>Fourth. Look in the repair parts list work packages for the Figure and item
                    numbers. The NSNs and part numbers are on the same line as the associated item
                    numbers.</item>
            </randlist>
            <seqlist>
                <item>When NSN Is Known.</item>
            </seqlist>
            <randlist>
                <item>First. If you have the NSN, look in the STOCK NUMBER column of the NSN index
                    work package. The NSN is arranged in NIIN sequence. Note the Figure and item
                    number next to the NSN. </item>
                <item>Second. Turn to the Figure and locate the item number. Verify that the item is
                    the one for which you are looking. </item>

            </randlist>
            <seqlist>
                <item>When Part Number Is Known.</item>
                <item>First. If you have the part number and not the NSN, look in the PART NUMBER
                    column of the part number index work package. Identify the Figure and item
                    number. Second. Look up the item on the Figure in the applicable repair parts
                    list work package. </item>
                <item>Second. Turn to the Figure and locate the item number. Verify that the item is
                    the one for which you are looking. <table>
                        <tgroup cols="2" tgroupstyle="nolabel">
                            <tbody>
                                <row>
                                    <entry align="center"><emphasis emph="uline"
                                            >Abbreviation</emphasis></entry>
                                    <entry align="center"><emphasis emph="uline"
                                            >Explanation</emphasis></entry>
                                </row>
                                <row>
                                    <entry>NONE</entry>
                                    <entry/>
                                </row>
                            </tbody>
                        </tgroup>
                    </table>
                </item>
            </seqlist>
        </para>
    </introwp>
	
    <plwp wpno="r15016" chngno="0">

	<!-- ********** FIGURE 15-016 ********** -->

        <wpidinfo>
            <maintlvl level="maintainer"/>
            <title>HYDRAULICS INSTALLATION</title>
        </wpidinfo>
        <pi.category>
            <figure id="R09150073">
                <title id="R09150073-Title-1">Hydraulics Installation</title>
                <subfig sheet="1" totalsheets="2">
                    <graphic boardno="R09150073"> </graphic>
                </subfig>
                <subfig sheet="2" totalsheets="2" id="R09150074">
                    <graphic boardno="R09150074"/>
                </subfig>
            </figure>
        	
        	<fncgrp>
                <fnccode>15 FRAME, TOWING ATTACHMENTS, AND DRAWBAR</fnccode>
                <fnctitle>Fig. 16 Hydraulics Installation</fnctitle>
            </fncgrp>
            <pi.item>
                <callout assocfig="R09150073-Fig-1" label="1"/>
                <qty>1</qty>
                <smr sourcecode="XD" maintcode="O" recovercode="DD"/>
                <nsn/>
                <partno>12595816</partno>
                <cageno>19207</cageno>
                <name>HOSE ASSEMBLY</name>
                <desc/>
            </pi.item>
            <pi.item>
                <callout assocfig="R09150073-Fig-1" label="2"/>
                <qty>1</qty>
                <smr sourcecode="XD" maintcode="O" recovercode="DD"/>
                <nsn/>
                <partno>12595817</partno>
                <cageno>19207</cageno>
                <name>HOSE ASSEMBLY</name>
                <desc/>
            </pi.item>
            <pi.item>
                <callout assocfig="R09150073-Fig-1" label="32"/>
                <qty>1</qty>
                <smr sourcecode="XD" maintcode="O" recovercode="DD"/>
                <nsn/>
                <partno>12595818</partno>
                <cageno>19207</cageno>
                <name>HOSE ASSEMBLY</name>
                <desc/>
            </pi.item>
        </pi.category>
    </plwp>
</pim>